OLIVER **THEK**

oliverthek@gmail.com · +36304917370

Organized and dependable Track Foreman with 4 years of experience conducting maintenance and repairs across the Hungarian railway system. Fully competent in the management of multiple priorities and teams with a willingness to take on added responsibilities to achieve group goals.

SKILLS

- Daily facility operations
- Safety improvements
- Task prioritization and delegation
- Daily maintenance and repairs logs
- Self-sufficient and a team player
- Hazard monitoring and management
- Operation of hand and power tools
- Comprehension of railway documents

EXPERIENCE

2019 - PRESENT

TRACK FOREMAN, HUNGARIAN STATE RAILWAYS / MAV

Oversees and coordinates teams of 10-12 personnel in the construction, maintenance, and repairs of railway track across the entire Hungarian railway system since 2022.

- Reports directly to the Stationmaster, receives daily work orders, and coordinates with them on the management and delegation of each task.
- Briefs the Stationmaster on the outcome of all daily activities.
- Primarily performs the duties of a supervisor and directs a crew of 2-8 laborers.
- Utilizes a range of small to large electric and motorized tools to make repairs, conduct major and minor maintenance and fulfill all landscaping duties.
- Manages and oversees all aspects of the track and railway maintenance; inspections, and conducts the replacement of rails, ties, switches, ballasts, and repairs track surface deviations, alignments, and gauges.
- Interprets documents that relate to track safety regulation, operation, and maintenance.

AUG 2008 - MAY 2013 VIDEO EDITOR, INDAVIDEO.HU

Editor of a Hungarian video sharing site and online newspaper, "Index".

- Worked closely with the Senior Editor and reported to them on all major decisions.
- Conducted the editing and cutting of online videos of the corresponding story.
- Provided occasional assistance with the filming of content for the stories.

MAY 2005 - MAY 2006 BAKER, ALDRED'S THE BAKERS

- Reported directly to the Head Baker and worked with a team of 20-30 people, 9h/day, 6 days a week.
- Removed an assortment of freshly baked goods directly from the oven and placed them in the appropriate area, ready to be sold.
- Prepared buns, rolls, and breads, making them presentable.
- Maintained a clean and tidy workplace.

OCT 2001 - MAY 2005

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR, HUNGARIAN STATE TREASURY (MAK)

Managed and supervised a network of 300 computers.

- Reported directly to the Department Manager.
- Performed duties as part of a 6-person team.
- Maintained and repaired the computer software and hardware of multiple departments within the treasury.
- Conducted a mass installation of the Oracle database across numerous institutions.

EDUCATION

1986 - 1995

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, JOZSEF KATONA HIGH SCHOOL

LICENSES & CERTIFICATES

SEPT 2020 - SEPT 2021

FOREMAN TRAINING CERTIFICATION, HUNGARIAN TRAFFIC

AUTHORITY

FEB 2023 - JUN 2024

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER AND TESTER CERTIFICATION, SZEKESFEHERVAR SZC SZECHENYI ISTVAN TECHNICAL TECH